const mathematicsQuestions = [
    {
        question : 'Calculate the total surface area of a cupboard which measures 12cm by 10cm by 8cm',
        options : ['1920cm²', '592cm²', '296cm²', '148cm²'],
        answer :'592cm²',
        duration : 10
    },
    {
        question : 'Convert 0.04945 to two significant figures',
        options : ['0.040', '0.049', '0.050', '0.49'],
        answer :'0.049',
        duration : 10
    },
    {
        question : 'The probability that james and john passed an examination are 3/4 and 3/5 respectively. find the probability of both boys failed the examination.',
        options : ['1/10', '2/10', '9/20', '11/20'],
        answer :'11/20',
        duration : 15
    },
    {
        question : 'What is the place value of 9 in the number 3.04923?',
        options : ['9/10000', '9/1000', '9/100', '9/10'],
        answer :'9/1000',
        duration : 10
    },
    {
        question : 'if the simple interest on a sum of money invested at 3% per annum for 2½ year is ₦123, find the principal',
        options : ['₦676.50', '₦820', '₦1,640', '₦4,920'],
        answer :'₦1,640',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'A machine valued at ₦20,000 depreciates by 10% every year. what will be the value of the machine at the end of two years?',
        options : ['₦16,200', '₦14,200', '₦12,000', '₦8,000'],
        answer :'₦16,200',
        duration : 25
    },
    {
        question : 'A boy walks 800m in 20mins. Calculate his average speed in kM/H',
        options : ['2.4', '4', '24', '40'],
        answer :'2.4',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'How many times, correct to the nearest whole number, will a man run round a circular track of diameter 100m to cover a distance of 1000m?',
        options : ['3', '4', '5', '6'],
        answer :'4',
        duration : 25
    },
    {
        question : 'Divide the L.C.M of 48, 64 and 80 by their H.C.F',
        options : ['20', '30', '48', '60'],
        answer :'60',
        duration : 25
    },
    {
        question : 'Integrate the expression 6x² - 2x + 1',
        options : ['3x³ - 2x² + x + c', '2x³ - x² + x + c', '2x³ - 3x² + c', 'x³ + x² - x + c'],
        answer :'2x³ - x² + x + c',
        duration : 25
    },
    {
        question : 'in how many ways can this latters LEADER be arranged',
        options : ['72', '144', '360', '720'],
        answer :'360',
        duration : 25
    },
    {
        question : 'Express 495g as a percentage of 16.5kg',
        options : ['3%', '3¹/3%', '15%', '30%'],
        answer :'3%',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Evaluate (2√3 - 4)(2√3 + 4)',
        options : ['-4', '-2', '2', '4'],
        answer :'-4',
        duration : 25
    },
    {
        question : 'Find the average of the first four prime numbers greater than 10',
        options : ['20', '19', '17', '15'],
        answer :'15',
        duration : 30
    },
    {
        question : 'Calculate the area of an equilateral triangle of sides 8cm',
        options : ['8√3', '16', '4√3', '16√3'],
        answer :'16√3',
        duration : 30
    },
]

console.log('maths')